<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright 2021 The University of Manchester
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->

<pages>
    <!-- Use ‘ instead of ' -->
    <page>
        <pageName>1-search-programme</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colRadio</pageElement>
            <helpText>After finding or listing a set of drug programmes, use the radio buttons below to
                select the drug programme that you wish to configure using the radio-button selector.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDrugID</pageElement>
            <helpText>The drug programme identifier</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colNStudies</pageElement>
            <helpText>The total number of studies within the drug programme that are know to  the ACUITY  system either
                via a link to the IMPACT data system, or that have been manually added through  the ACUITY  system.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colNAcuityStudies</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number of studies that have been enabled for further
                configuration (e.g. data mapping) in ACUITY
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colAcuityEnabled</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether the drug programme itself has been previously set up within  the ACUITY  system.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colAction</pageElement>
            <helpText>Provides a link to the summary of the set up for and drug programmes that have been ACUITY-enabled.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>2-edit-programme</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>drugProgrammeID</pageElement>
            <helpText>The drug programme identifier</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>drugProgrammeName</pageElement>
            <helpText>This is the name that will be visible in ACUITY and VA Security. Spotfire files will be named
                using the Drug Programme ID.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>programmeEnabled</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether the drug programme itself has previously been set up within  the ACUITY  system.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studyNumberStudies</pageElement>
            <helpText>The total number of studies within the drug programme that are known to  the ACUITY  system
                either via link to the IMPACT data system, or have been enabled for further configuration.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studyNumberEnabledStudies</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number of studies that have been enabled for further
                configuration (e.g. data mapping) in ACUITY
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>chiefProgramme</pageElement>
            <helpText>The name of the individual who will have the primary responsibility for administering ACUITY
                for this drug project. Current guidance indicates this should be the Medical Science Director. This
                field is used to help  the ACUITY  team manage ACUITY  for drug programmes.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>ownerProgramme</pageElement>
            <helpText>The name of the individual who will have the responsibility of authorising access for other
                users to  the ACUITY  visualisations for this drug programme. Current guidance indicates that this should
                be the Medical Science Director. This field is used by  the ACUITY  team to set up processes for
                authorisation to see study data.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>createDashboard</pageElement>
            <helpText>A programme-level view displaying high-level study counts,
                which are important to ascertain current progress for a particular drug.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>4-setup-groupings</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>groupType</pageElement>
            <helpText>Select the type of grouping that you wish to create. The options are adverse event groupings,
                where different preferred terms can be grouped, or lab measurement groupings whereby different types of
                lab measurement can be grouped. The idea is that this allows a customisable way to group together sets of
                patient data that are of particular interest to your drug programme.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>groupingName</pageElement>
            <helpText>Each grouping must have a unique name, but it is up to you what name you use. We recommend you use
                a name that is fairly explanatory so that your group is identifiable at other stages in the ACUITY
                configuration.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>defaultValue</pageElement>
            <helpText>The default group value is the values for the group name that will be assigned to any adverse
                event (for adverse event groupings) or lab measurement (for lab measurement groups) that
                are not explicitly assigned to a group in the data provided by the user. For clarity, we recommend
                you use a value such as "not assigned to a group".
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>dataLocation</pageElement>
            <helpText>Here you must either provide the location of the data file which holds (or will hold) the grouping
                information, or select to perform manual entry. If you are uploading a file, the format of that file
                must be as two columns, where the first column holds the name of the groups and the seconds column
                holds the terms being grouped. The file should be comma-separated (.csv) text file.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>headerRow</pageElement>
            <helpText>Check the box if the file you wish to upload has a header row. Header rows will not be used in
                these groupings.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>dataReady</pageElement>
            <helpText>Check the box if the grouping you are creating is appropriate to be used in ACUITY  visualisations.
                Leaving the box unchecked will mean that although your grouping configuration will be stored, the
                groupin will not be available for use in ACUITY  visualisations.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colGroupingName</pageElement>
            <helpText>Grouping names uniquely identify each user-defined data grouping to be identifiable
                at other stages in the ACUITY configuration.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colTypeOfGroup</pageElement>
            <helpText>The grouping type refers to what sort of variable is being grouped. Adverse event groupings group
                different MedDRA preferred terms and lab measurement groupings group sets of lab measurements types
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDataSource</pageElement>
            <helpText>The data source refers to the source of grouping data. This may be a file, or the
                data may have been entered manually through this interface.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colAcuityEnabled</pageElement>
            <helpText>ACUITY enabled being checked means that the groupings can be used in ACUITY  visualisations. Go to
                "Edit Settings" to change the value of this checkbox.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colLastEdited</pageElement>
            <helpText>Shows the name of the user who last edited this grouping.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDate</pageElement>
            <helpText>Shows the date when this grouping was last edited.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colAeGroupName</pageElement>
            <helpText>In this column you can view and edit the group names. Group names are user-defined, but we
                recommend that these names capture the rationale behind the group. Note that group names are
                case-sensitive. You can click in the table cells to make edits to the group names, then click
                on Save to store your changes.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colMedDra</pageElement>
            <helpText>In this column, you can view and edit the adverse events preferred terms, or lab measurement
                preferred names being grouped. You can click in the table cells to make edits to the group names,
                then click on Save to store your changes.
            </helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>colLabGroupingName</pageElement>
            <helpText>In this column you can view and edit the group names.
                Group names are user-defined, but we recommend that these names capture the rationale behind the group.
                Note that group names are case-sensitive. You can click in the table cells to make edits to the
                group names, then click on Save to store your changes.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colLabcodeValue</pageElement>
            <helpText>In this column, you can view and edit labcode for each Lab grouping. You can click
                in the table cells to make edits to the group names, then click on Save to store your changes.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colLabDescription</pageElement>
            <helpText>In this column, you can view and edit the description for labcode.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>admin</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>drugProgrammes</pageElement>
            <helpText>Here we list the drug programmes that have been configured to use ACUITY. You may add a new drug
                programme, edit an existing drug programme, or remove an existing drug programme configuration using
                the buttons below. Selecting a drug programme from a list will allow you to view the clinical study
                data sets and ACUITY  visualisation modules that have been configured for the programme.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>clinicalStudyDataSets</pageElement>
            <helpText>Here we list the clinical study data sets that have been configured to use ACUITY  for the drug
                programme selected, above. You may add a new study configuration, edit an existing study configuration,
                or remove an existing study configuration using the buttons below.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>visualisationModules</pageElement>
            <helpText>Here we list the visualisation modules that have been configured for the drug programme selected.
                You may add a new visualisation module, edit an existing visualisation module, or remove an existing
                visualisation module using the buttons below.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>1-search-study</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colStudyID</pageElement>
            <helpText>The dataset identifier</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colStudyName</pageElement>
            <helpText>The name of the clinical study</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colPhase</pageElement>
            <helpText>The clinical study phase</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colStudySetupStatus</pageElement>
            <helpText>The setup status of the study in ACUITY.

                "Not added to ACUITY" indicates that the study is not ready to be configured in ACUITY  as the parent drug
                programme has not been set up to allow this study to be configured. To remedy this you can reconfigure
                the drug programme.

                "Ready to map" indicates that the drug programme has been set up to allow this study to be configured,
                but no study configuration has yet been recorded.

                "Mapping in progress" indicates that the study configuration is underway, but incomplete.

                "Previously mapped" indicates that the mapping is sufficiently complete and enabled such that ACUITY  can
                use the study data in visualisations.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>2-edit-study</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>drugID</pageElement>
            <helpText>The drug programme identifier. This field is important for the organisation of date in ACUITY
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studyID</pageElement>
            <helpText>The dataset identifier. This field is important for the organisation of data in ACUITY
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studyName</pageElement>
            <helpText>The name of the dataset. This field is for user reference only and does not affect the data
                processing in ACUITY.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>clinicalStudyId</pageElement>
            <helpText>The clinical study identifier. This field is important for the organisation of data in ACUITY
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>clinicalStudyName</pageElement>
            <helpText>The name of the clinical study. This field is for user reference only and does not affect the data
                processing in ACUITY.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studyPhase</pageElement>
            <helpText>The clinical study phase. This field is for user reference only and does not affect the data
                processing in ACUITY.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studyType</pageElement>
            <helpText>The type of study, such as dose-finding. This field is for user reference only and does not affect
                the data processing in ACUITY.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studyDeliveryModel</pageElement>
            <helpText>The organisational process through which the study is being made, e.g., run by internal AZ R&amp;D.
                This field is for user reference only and does not affect the data processing in ACUITY.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>subjectPlannedDate</pageElement>
            <helpText>For prospective studies this should be an estimate of the date when the first subject will be dosing.
                For studies that have already begun, this should approximate the actual date for first subject dosing.
                This date can be modified as more is known about the study organisation. This date will be used
                to help  the ACUITY  team establish when data updates are likely to being.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>dbPlannedDate</pageElement>
            <helpText>This should be an estimate for when the primary database lock will occur. This date can be
                modified according to the progression of the study. This date will be used to help the ACUITY
                team establish when  the ACUITY  system should be shut down for the study
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studyPrimarySource</pageElement>
            <helpText>The folder location where the source files are stored. This is usually the CAVE location
                for this study‘s SAS files. This field allows the user to designate the location for the
                automatic mapping functions to search for the correct files.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>blinded</pageElement>
            <helpText>This field refers to whether the study has a blinding aspect. This field is critically important
                for correct use of data in ACUITY. If you are unsure of the correct value, or if this status has not
                yet been decided, select "Blinded" as this will ensure that the integrity of the study is not compromised.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>randomised</pageElement>
            <helpText>This field refers to whether the study subjects are randomised between study arms. This field is
                critically important for the correct use of data in ACUITY. If you are unsure of the correct value, or if this
                status has not yet been decided, then select "Randomised" as this will ensure that the integrity of the study is not
                compromised.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>regulatory</pageElement>
            <helpText>This field refers to whether the study will deliver or support a licensing submission. This field
                is critically important for the correct use of data in ACUITY. If you are unsure of the correct value, or if this
                status has not yet been decided, then select "Regulatory" as this will ensure that the integrity of the study is not
                compromised.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>cBioProfiles</pageElement>
            <helpText>Only applicable if including genomic data (for the Genomic Profile visualisation)
                and the link out to cBio is required. Information required by cBioPortal.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>amlEnabledForStudy</pageElement>
            <helpText>Enabling will allow relevant data to be sent to Azure Machine Learning Studio. It will be possible to view outcomes in the Machine Insights QT Interval plot.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>3-edit-mappings</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>dataType</pageElement>
            <helpText>Select the type of data that is being mapped into ACUITY  from the drop-down list.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>dataLocation</pageElement>
            <helpText>Here you must either provide the location of the data file which holds (or will hold) the grouping
                information. The files can either be SAS (sas7bdat) or a comma-separated (.csv) text file. If the
                file location is yet to be established, but you want to start mapping configuration, choose the upper option.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>whatWithData</pageElement>
            <helpText>Check the box if the data mapped is appropriate and correctly configured to be used in ACUITY
                visualisations. Leaving the box unchecked will mean that although your configuration will be stored,
                the data will not be available for use in ACUITY  visualisations.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colTypeOfInfo</pageElement>
            <helpText>Displays the type of data that is being mapped into ACUITY</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDataSource</pageElement>
            <helpText>Displays the location of the source data, if known.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colAcuityEnabled</pageElement>
            <helpText>ACUITY enabled being checked means that the data can be used in ACUITY  visualisations. Go to "Edit
                Settings" to change the value of this checkbox.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colLastEdited</pageElement>
            <helpText>Shows the name of the user who last edited this grouping.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDate</pageElement>
            <helpText>Shows the date when this grouping was last edited.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDataField</pageElement>
            <helpText>The name of  the ACUITY  data field.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colSourceData</pageElement>
            <helpText>The name of the column in the source data that maps to  the ACUITY  data field. You may add more than
                one column, to do this put multiple column names separated by commas.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDecodingInfo</pageElement>
            <helpText>Some data, particularly data in SAS files, is coded into integers. In order for ACUITY  to extract
                some meaningful values, information about how to change codes to meaningful values may be required.
                To do this, you must first
                configure the mapping for a value decoding file. The value entered into this column must be equivalent to a value that will appear
                in the "code group name" field of that value decoding file.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDefaultValue</pageElement>
            <helpText>A default value that will be assigned to  the ACUITY  field in the case where no equivalent column
                exists in the source data, or where the value in the source data is blank.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colAggregation</pageElement>
            <helpText>These aggregation functions allow  the ACUITY  system to make sense of some of the more complicated
                data mapping requirements for ACUITY. For most mapped data, no aggregation is required. However, for date
                values  the ACUITY  system must be told whether it is the day, or month, that appear first in the date
                representation. In addition, the user can make ACUITY  system take the maximum value from a set
                of numerical columns. This is particularly useful when a maximum CTC grade must be taken from a set
                of different CTC values.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colMandatory</pageElement>
            <helpText>This column indicates whether the field in question is mandatory, or not. For a data table mapping
                to be considered complete, all mandatory fields must be mapped, whereas other fields are optional.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>study-setup-main</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>dataChecklist</pageElement>
            <helpText>The Data Checklist provides a summary of the mapping progress for the study date. Information
                types that are not completely mapped (where not all mandatory fields are mapped to a source data file
                column) are shown with a red question mark and information types that are completely mapped to
                a minimum acceptable level are shown with a green tick mark. Note that a green tick mark does not
                necessarily indicate that your choice of mapping is accurate! In addition, for a study to be considered
                to be ready for use in one or more ACUITY  visualisation modules, all of the information types listed
                as "Mandatory patient information" must be completely mapped.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>4-edit-groupings</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colGroupingName</pageElement>
            <helpText>Grouping names uniquely identify each user-defined subject grouping and allow the grouping
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDataSource</pageElement>
            <helpText>The data source refers to the source of grouping data. This may be a file, or the data may have
                been entered manually
                through this interface.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colAcuityEnabled</pageElement>
            <helpText>ACUITY enabled being checked means that the data can be used in ACUITY  visualisations. Go to "Edit
                Settings" to change the
                value of this checkbox.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colLastEdited</pageElement>
            <helpText>Shows the name of the user who last edited this grouping.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDate</pageElement>
            <helpText>Shows the date when this grouping was last edited.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colSubjectID</pageElement>
            <helpText>In this column you can view and edit the group names. Group names are user-defined, but we
                recommend that these names capture the rationale behind the group. Note that group names are
                case-sensitive. You can click in the table cells to make edits to the group names, then click
                on Save to store your changes.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colGroupName</pageElement>
            <helpText>In this column you can view and edit the adverse events preferred terms, or lab measurement
                preferred names being grouped. You can click in the table cells to make edits to the group names,
                then click on Save to store your changes.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>5-study-setup-summary</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studySummary</pageElement>
            <helpText>The dataset summary provides an overview of the clinical study dataset setup. you should check
                this is correct before finishing the setup
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>dataMappings</pageElement>
            <helpText>Here we show a summary of the data mappings for the clinical study</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>altSubjectGroupings</pageElement>
            <helpText>Here we show a summary of the alternative subject groupings for the clinical study.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>disclaimer</pageElement>
            <helpText>For this study to be used in ACUITY, we must be sure that all of the set up is appropriate. In
                particular, the blinding, randomisation and regulatory statuses of the set up are correct and that
                no inappropriate (e.g. unblinding) subject groups have been created. To confirm the setup is
                correct you must indicate this in the disclaimer.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>history</pageElement>
            <helpText>Here we record the history of study set up confirmation so that it is clear who has taken
                responsibility for confirmation and when confirmation was granted.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>1-project-and-study</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>projectTable</pageElement>
            <helpText>Select the drug programme for which you wish to create a set of ACUITY  visualisations. Note that
                only drug programmes that have been configured for ACUITY  are displayed.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studyTable</pageElement>
            <helpText>Select the datasets for which you wish to create a set of ACUITY  visualisations. Note only
                clinical studies that have been configured for ACUITY  are displayed. You must select at least one study.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>2-project-groupings</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>aeGroupings</pageElement>
            <helpText>Select the adverse event groupings you wish to include in your ACUITY  visualisations. Selecting a
                grouping is not essential for ACUITY  set up. In order to set up a new adverse event grouping you should
                visit the drug programme setup.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>labGroupings</pageElement>
            <helpText>Select the lab measurement groupings you wish to include in your ACUITY  visualisations. Selecting a
                grouping is not essential for ACUITY  set up. In order to set up a new adverse event grouping you should
                visit the drug programme setup.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>3-instance-settings</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>selectModule</pageElement>
            <helpText>ACUITY modules are sets of visualisations tailored to explore a particular aspect of the clinical
                studies. The current choices available are ACUITY Safety (designed to allow exploration of safety-related
                signals in the data) and ACUITY  Tolerability (designed to allow exploration of the drug tolerability).
                Further modules may be added over time. You will only be allowed to choose modules that are appropriate
                based on the types of studies you have selected.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>Each set of ACUITY  visualisations must be given a unique name, this will be used as the analysis
                file name. The first part of the name is standard and has been completed for you. Try to use short,
                but meaningful names. For example, "ACUITY_Safety_STDY4321_study1"
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>4-study-groupings</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>studyName</pageElement>
            <helpText>Select the alternative subject groupings you wish to include in your ACUITY  visualisations.
                Selecting a grouping is not essential for ACUITY  set up. In order to set up a new adverse event
                grouping you should visit the drug programme setup.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>biomarkerGroupings</pageElement>
            <helpText>Select the biomarker groupings you wish to include in your ACUITY  Oncology visualisations.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>5-views</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>moduleLabel</pageElement>
            <helpText>ACUITY views are visualisations tailored to explore a particular aspect of the clinical study. Here
                you may select any views that are appropriate for the type of studies within  the ACUITY  module.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>warnings</pageElement>
            <helpText>Warnings indicate the reasons why certain ACUITY  views are not available. This may be due to a lack
                of source data, in which case you may be able to revisit the clinical study setup and provide further
                mappings, or because the type of view is not appropriate for the type of study (based on the
                randomisation, blinding and regulatory statuses of the studies).
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>6-summary</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>acuityName</pageElement>
            <helpText>This summary provides an overview of  the ACUITY  module that will be set up. Before finishing the
                setup, you should check whether this information is correct.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>confirmation</pageElement>
            <helpText>For theseACUITY  visualisations to be created, you should ensure that the configuration is
                appropriate. In particular, you should consider that after creation, all authorised users will have
                access to this visualisation through ACUITY. You can confirm the configuration is correct and continue
                to create this ACUITY  instance by confirmation in the disclaimer, then pressing the Finish button.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>dataMappings</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Somatic status</pageElement>
            <helpText>
                1. ‘Somatic status‘ should equal one of the following values:
                &#9;&#8226; ‘known‘
                &#9;&#8226; ‘likely‘
                &#9;&#8226; ‘unknown‘
                2. ‘known‘ or ‘likely‘ values will be shown in the Genomic Profile
                3. ‘unknown‘ values will not be shown in the Genomic Profile
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Variant type</pageElement>
            <helpText>
                1. ‘Variant-type‘ should equal one of the following values:
                &#9;&#8226; ‘short-variant‘
                &#9;&#8226; ‘copy number alteration‘
                &#9;&#8226; ‘rearrangement‘
                2. When the value is:
                &#9;&#8226; ‘short-variant‘ the mutation type field is taken from ‘Mutation type‘ in the data structure
                &#9;&#8226; ‘copy number alteration‘ the mutation type field is taken from ‘Copy number alteration type‘ in the data structure
                &#9;&#8226; ‘rearrangement‘ the mutation type field is taken from ‘Rearrangement description‘ in the data structure
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Mutation type</pageElement>
            <helpText>For a field to appear as NULL in the plot the cell must be empty.
                If the dataset has e.g. a ‘-‘ to denote NULL then use the decoding function along with an entry in the
                ‘cntlin‘ file.
                The Mutation type field in the data structure is used for mutation type when variant type = ‘short variant‘.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Copy number alteration type</pageElement>
            <helpText>For a field to appear as NULL in the plot the cell must be empty.
                If the dataset has e.g. a ‘-‘ to denote NULL then use the decoding function along with an entry in the
                ‘cntlin‘ file.
                The Copy number alteration type (CNA_TYPE) field in the data structure is used for mutation when variant type = ‘copy number alteration‘.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Rearrangement description</pageElement>
            <helpText>For a field to appear as NULL in the plot the cell must be empty.
                If the dataset has e.g. a ‘-‘ to denote NULL then use the decoding function along with an entry in the
                ‘cntlin‘ file.
                The Rearrangement description (REARR_DESCRIPTION) field in the data structure is used for mutation when variant type = rearrangement.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Action Taken, Study Drug</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value describing the type of change being made to the dosing schedule</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE description</pageElement>
            <helpText>A String value that can hold further description of the serious adverse event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE End Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the adverse event ended</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE Start Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the adverse event began</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE End Time</pageElement>
            <helpText>The time of day at which the adverse event ended</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE Start Time</pageElement>
            <helpText>The time of day at which the adverse event began</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE Term</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value describing the type of adverse event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Any New Lesions Since Baseline (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether any new lesions have been identified since the baseline measurement
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Any Non Target Lesion Present (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether or not any non-target lesions were present at the time of the
                non-target lesion assessment
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Any Target Lesion Present (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether ir not any target lesion was found to be present at the time of
                target lesion assessment
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Assessment Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the vital measurements were performed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>ATC code</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the Anatomical Therapeutic Chemical unique identifier for the medication
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>ATC code text</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the Anatomical Therapeutic Chemical identifier for the medication full name
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Centre Number</pageElement>
            <helpText>A unique integer value for the study centre</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Code group name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string that acts as a group name used to group together distinct sets of codes and their
                corresponding decoded values
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Coded value</pageElement>
            <helpText>An integer value ‘code‘ that that can be decoded into a meaningful value.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Congenital Anomaly or Birth Defect</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether or not the serious adverse event caused a congenital abnormality
                or birth defect
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date AE Met Criteria for Serious AE</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the serious adverse event met the Serious criteria</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date Investigator Aware of Serious AE</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which investigator became aware of the Serious adverse event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of Birth</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date of birth of the subject</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of ECG</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the ECG was performed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of Hospitalization</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the subject was hospitalised due to the serious adverse event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of death</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the subject died</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of Discharge</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the subject was discharged from hospital</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of Investigational Product Discontinuation</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the study drug was discontinued</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Subject Decision Specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the subject decision specification</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other Subject Decision Specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the other subject decision specification</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of the Measurement</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the measurement was made</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Decoded value</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string that is the meaningful (decoded) that can be translated from a coded value</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Diastolic Blood Pressure</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value giving the diastolic blood pressure</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Dose Frequency</pageElement>
            <helpText>An integer value denoting the frequency with which the medication is administered to the subject
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Dosing Frequency</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that describes the dosing frequency, e.g., "BID" for twice -daily.
                This field will be used in precedence over the dosing frequency per interval and interval unit fields.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Dosing Frequency (per Interval)</pageElement>
            <helpText>An integer value denoting the frequency with which the study drug is administered to the subject
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Dosing Frequency Interval Unit</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the unit in which the dosing frequency is measured</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Dose Frequency Unit</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the unit in which the medication frequency is measured</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Dose per Administration</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value giving the dose of medication given to the subject per administration
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Dose Unit</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the unit in which the dose amount is measured</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>End date of concomitant medication</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the medication regimen ended</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>End date/time of the dose schedule</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the dosing schedule ended</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Free text where the reason is specified.</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value providing the further reasons for which the study drug was discontinued</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Height</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number giving the height of the subject</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Imaging Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the LVEF imaging was performed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Investigator Opinion Agrees with RECIST Response (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether or not the investigator opinion of response agrees with the RECIST
                response
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Investigator Opinion of Patient Status</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value giving the investigator opinion of response</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Left Ventricular Ejection Fraction</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value denoting the LVEF</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Lower reference Value</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value that gives the lower reference range value for the laboratory test result for
                the subject
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Laboratory Test Identifier</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string identifier denoting what sort of laboratory measurement was made</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Laboratory Test Unit</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the units in which the laboratory value is measured</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Laboratory Value</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value that gives the value for the laboratory test result</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Life Threatening (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether or not the adverse event was life threatening</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Longest Diameter of Target Lesion</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value denoting the longest diameter of the target lesion</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>LVEF Method</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the method by which the LVEF was measured</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>LVEF Method, Other</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that describes any alternative method used to measure the LVEF</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Main Reason for Action Taken, Study Drug</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value describing the main reason for change being made to the dosing schedule</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Main reason for Investigational Product Discontinuation</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value providing the main reason for which the study drug was discontinued</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MEDDRA Higher-Level Term</pageElement>
            <helpText>A MedDRA Higher-Level Term Name string assigned to the adverse event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MEDDRA Low-Level Term</pageElement>
            <helpText>A MedDRA Low-Level Term Name string assigned to the adverse event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MEDDRA Preferred term.</pageElement>
            <helpText>A MedDRA Preferred Term Name string assigned to the adverse event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MEDDRA System Organ Class</pageElement>
            <helpText>A MedDRA System Organ class abbreviation or name string assigned to the adverse event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MEDDRA Version</pageElement>
            <helpText>The MedDRA version used to code the adverse event, e.g, 4.0</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medication Group</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that denotes the group of medications to which the medication belongs.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medication Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the name of the medication</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Maximum severity grade</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that denotes the maximum severity grade experienced for the given AE, either using
                AE CTC grading or AE Intensity grading.
            </helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Starting severity grade for AE</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that denotes the initial starting severity grade for the given AE,
                either using AE CTC grading or AE Intensity grading.
            </helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>AE severity grade changes</pageElement>
            <helpText>AE severity grade values denoted by either CTC or AE Intensity, over time. Where multiple severity
                grade columns are provided, these should be entered in the order that they occurred, separated by
                commas, corresponding to the dates provided in the "AE severity change dates (mm/dd/yyyy)" column. Note that the
                "Multiple AE severity grade changes" aggregation function must be selected for this to work.
            </helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>AE severity change dates (mm/dd/yyyy)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Date values that when changes in severity grade over time happened. Where multiple date columns
                are provided, these should be entered in order, separated by commas, corresponding to the severity
                values provided in the "AE severity grade changes" column, and the "Multiple AE severity grade changes"
                aggregation function must be selected.
            </helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>New Lesion Site</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that denotes the site occupied by the a new lesion</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>New Lesion Date of Scan/Clinical Examination</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the new lesion assessment was performed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Non-Target Lesion Date of Scan/Clinical Examination</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the non-target lesion was assessed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>O2 Saturation Level</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number giving the O2 saturation level for the subject</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Original Diagnosis Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the subject was originally diagnosed with the disease</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other Serious/Important Medically Event</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether or not the serious adverse event caused a congenital abnormality
                or birth defect
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other Medication or Drug that Caused AE</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value specifying the name of the medication or drug other than the investigational
                product that caused the serious adverse event
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Overall ECG evaluation</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that summarises the ECG evaluation</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Clinically Significant</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting whether the ECG value captured has clinical significance</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Persist. or Sign. Disability/Incapacity</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether or not the serious adverse event caused persisting signs of
                disability or incapacity
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>PR interval duration</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number vaalue giving the PR interval duration from the ECG measurement</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Primary Tumor Location</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string that describes the location of the primary tumour</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Pulse Rate</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value giving the pulse rate</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>QRS Duration</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value giving the QRS duration from the ECG measurement</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>QT interval duration</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value giving the QT interval duration from the ECG measurement</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Race</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that denotes the race of the subject</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason, Abnormal Overall ECG Evaluation</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that describes reasons why the overall ECG evaluation was summarised to be
                abnormal
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Indication</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the reason why the treatment was administered to the subject</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason for Study Drug Dose Change Specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value describing further reason for change being made to the dosing schedule</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason RECIST and Investigator Assessments Differ</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that describes the reason for which the RECIST response and investigator opinion of
                response differ.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reasonable Possibility AE Caused by Investigational Product (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether the adverse event was probably caused by the investigational
                product.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>RECIST Response</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that provides the overall response of the subject at the time of assessment
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Requires or Prolongs Hospitalization</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether or the serious adverse event prolonged or required
                hospitalisation
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Response of Non-Target Lesions</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that summarises the response of the non-target lesions at the time of assessment
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Results in Death (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether or not the subject died as a result of the adverse event(s)
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>RR interval duration</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number vaalue giving the RR interval duration from the ECG measurement</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>SAE Caused by Other Medication</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether or not the serious adverse event was caused by medication other
                than the investigational product
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>SAE Caused by Study Procedure(s)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value specifying whether the serious adverse event was caused as a result of the clinical
                study procedure
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Sampling Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the sample for the laboratory test was taken</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Serious AE (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting whether the adverse event was of the serious category</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Sex</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that denotes the sex of the subject</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Site of Non-Target Lesion</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the site occupied by the non-target lesion</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Site of Target Lesion</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value denoting the site occupied by the assessed target lesion</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Specify Primary Tumor Location</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string description with further information describing the location of the primary tumour
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Start date of concomitant medication</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the medication regimen began</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Start date/time of the dose schedule</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the dosing schedule began</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Study Drug Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string that uniquely identifies the name of the study drug (otherwise known as the
                "investigational product")
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Study identifier</pageElement>
            <helpText>A unique string identifier for the clinical study that will be used to identify the study
                throughout other data files.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Study part identifier</pageElement>
            <helpText>A unique string identifier for the study part identifier that will be used to identify the study
                part throughout other data files.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Study Procedure(s) that Caused AE</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value specifying the aspect of the study procedure that caused the serious adverse
                event
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Subject group name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value giving the name of the subject group</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Subject grouping name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value used to name the set of patient groupings that have been mapped in this file,
                such as "Dose Cohorts". A default value may be applied here.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Subject identifier</pageElement>
            <helpText>A unique string identifier for the subject that will be used to identify the subject throughout
                other data files. The enrolment code is recommended.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Systolic Blood Pressure</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value giving the systolic blood pressure</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Target Lesion Number</pageElement>
            <helpText>A string value that is the unique identifier for the target lesion that is assessed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Target Lesion Date of Scan/Clinical Examination</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the target lesion was assessed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Upper Reference Value</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number value that gives the upper reference range value for the laboratory test result for
                the subject
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Visit Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>A date value for the visit on which the subject was enrolled.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Visit Number</pageElement>
            <helpText>An integer value denoting the number of the visit</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Vital.Module</pageElement>
            <helpText>The Vital.Module column is required when multiple vitals measurements from the same assessment
                time point are listed on separate rows. For example, height and weight on one row and O2 saturation on
                a separate row but all with the same measurement date. As these rows will show different module
                identifiers,  the ACUITY  system can use the module column to ensure that the data is pooled, rather
                than one row overwriting another.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Weight</pageElement>
            <helpText>A real number giving the weight of the subject</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Specimen identifier</pageElement>
            <helpText>The identifier for the specimen</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Specimen collection date/time</pageElement>
            <helpText>The actual date and time when the sample specimen was collected</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Specimen collection category</pageElement>
            <helpText>The category of specimen, relating to the purpose for collection, e.g., "PK, Biofluid"</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Protocol schedule</pageElement>
            <helpText>A text representation of the time point in relation to the study protocol</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Protocol schedule day</pageElement>
            <helpText>A numerical representation of the time point, days</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Protocol schedule hour</pageElement>
            <helpText>A numerical representation of the time point, hours</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Protocol schedule minute</pageElement>
            <helpText>A numerical representation of the time point, minutes</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date/time of investigational drug administration</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date and time of the investigational drug administration to which the specimen collection
                relates
            </helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Analyte</pageElement>
            <helpText>The name of the analyte, expected to be a drug identifier</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Analyte concentration</pageElement>
            <helpText>The concentration of the analyte in the sample</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Analyte concentration unit</pageElement>
            <helpText>The unit of concentration for the measurement of the analyte</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Lower limit of quantification</pageElement>
            <helpText>The lower limit of quantification for the analyte in the sample</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Cycle</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number, or text explanation for the cycle of treatment at the time of sampling</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Treatment</pageElement>
            <helpText>A short description of the treatment the subject is undertaking</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Treatment/protocol dose</pageElement>
            <helpText>A short description of the treatment the subject is undertaking
                or the dose specified in the protocol</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Treatment schedule</pageElement>
            <helpText>A short description of the treatment schedule the subject is undertaking</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Comment</pageElement>
            <helpText>A comment that accompanies the concentration result</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Visit name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A text representation of the visit, e.g., Cycle 0 Day 01</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Lesion No Longer Measurable</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describing why the target lesion has not been measured</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Method of Assessment</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting the method of assessment of the target lesion</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Parameter</pageElement>
            <helpText>A description of the PK parameter being expressed, e.g., "Cmin"</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Withdrawal / Completion Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date that the subject withdrew from or completed the study</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Prematurely Withdrawn</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether the subject prematurely withdrew rather than completed the study</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason for Withdrawal/Completion</pageElement>
            <helpText>The main reason why the subject prematurely withdrew</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Withdrawal/Completion Specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>An explanation of the reason for premature withdrawal</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Ethnic Population</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number, expected to be an ethnic population identifier</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other Ethnic Population</pageElement>
            <helpText>The text explanation of other ethnic population</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Assessment date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the e-Diary assessment was captured</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Time for study drug intake</pageElement>
            <helpText>The time of day at which study drug intake occurred</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Device or study drug name</pageElement>
            <helpText>The name that identifies the type of device or study drug whose intake is being recorded
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Assessment time (morning)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The time of day that the morning assessment was recorded</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>PEF morning (L/min)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The peak expiratory flow recorded at the morning assessment, in L/min</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Assessment time (evening)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The time of day that the evening assessment was recorded</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>PEF evening (L/min)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The peak expiratory flow recorded at the evening assessment, in L/min</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Asthma symptom score (night-time)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The asthma symptom score for the night</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Asthma symptom score (day-time)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The asthma symptom score for the day</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Woke due to asthma</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether one or more awakenings can be attributed to asthma symptoms</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Sample ID</pageElement>
            <helpText>Sample ID</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Median exon coverage</pageElement>
            <helpText>Median exon coverage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Disease</pageElement>
            <helpText>Disease</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Known somatic short variants</pageElement>
            <helpText>Known somatic short variants (percent-reads, coverage)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Likely somatic short variants</pageElement>
            <helpText>Likely somatic short variants (percent-reads, coverage)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>High-level amplifications</pageElement>
            <helpText>High-level (CN>8) and focal (CN>5) amplifications of genes amplifications of genes known to be
                recurrently amplified in cancer (copy number, exons)
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Low-level amplifications</pageElement>
            <helpText>Non-focal lower-level (CN&lt;=8) amplifications of genes known to be recurrently amplified in
                cancer (copy-number, exons)
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Homozygous deletions</pageElement>
            <helpText>Homozygous deletions of genes known to be recurrently deleted in cancer (0, exons)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Likely functional rearrangements</pageElement>
            <helpText>Likely functional rearrangements (e.g., gene fusions) (gene1_gene2_genomic event
                description_supporting-reads)
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Comments</pageElement>
            <helpText>Comments</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE Outcome</pageElement>
            <helpText>Current state of the AE, e.g. "Recovered/Resolved", Recovering/Resolving", etc.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Dose Limiting Toxicity</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag to specify that this AE defined the upper limit of dosing</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Time Point for Dose Limiting Toxicity</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the timepoint for dose limiting toxicity, such as a cycle number, visit
                number or date.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Immune-mediated AE</pageElement>
            <helpText>AE driven by immune system imbalance</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Infusion Reaction AE</pageElement>
            <helpText>AE relates to the administration of drug via IV infusion</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE Required Treatment</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag to specify that this AE required treatment.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE Caused Subject Withdrawal</pageElement>
            <helpText>AE resulted in the subject having to or choosing to withdraw from the study</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Action taken</pageElement>
            <helpText>Action taken</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Investigational drug names</pageElement>
            <helpText>Investigational drug names</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Additional drug names</pageElement>
            <helpText>Additional drug names</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Initial action taken for investigational drugs</pageElement>
            <helpText>Initial action taken for investigational drugs</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Initial action taken for additional drugs</pageElement>
            <helpText>Initial action taken for additional drugs</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Action taken due to severity grade changes for investigational drugs</pageElement>
            <helpText>Action taken due to severity grade changes for investigational drugs</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Action taken due to severity grade changes for additional drugs</pageElement>
            <helpText>Action taken due to severity grade changes for additional drugs</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Causality for investigational drugs</pageElement>
            <helpText>Causality for investigational drugs</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Causality for additional drugs</pageElement>
            <helpText>Causality for additional drugs</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Substance category</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the substance use category</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Substance use occurrence</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the usage occurrence (never, current, former)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Type of substance</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the type of the substance</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other substance type specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes alternative type of the substance</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Substance consumption</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the substance consumption (Units)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Frequency</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes frequency interval of the substance usage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Visit Number</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number of the subject visit. Please enter a numeric value only to this field.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>PT Visit Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date of the subject visit</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>PT Sampling Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the measurement was made</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>PT Serum</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting the result of pregnancy test - Serum (positive or negative)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>PT Urine</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting the result of pregnancy test - Urine (positive or negative)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>PT Plasma</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting the result of pregnancy test - Plasma (positive or negative)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Pregnancy Test</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting the result of pregnancy test (positive or negative)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Category</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes substance use category</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Sub Type</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes type of substance</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other Type Specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes alternative type of substance</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Sub Use Occurrence</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes usage occurrence (never, current, former)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Current Use Specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes current substance use specification (habitual or occasional)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Substance Type Use Occurrence</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the substance type usage occurrence</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Current Substance Use Specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the current substance use specification (habitual or occasional)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Substance Use End Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>A date on which the subject ended substance usage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Substance Use Start Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>A date on which the subject started substance usage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Substance Type</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the type of the substance</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Substance Use Frequency Interval</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes frequency interval of the substance usage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Use Start Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the subject started substance usage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Use End Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the subject ended substance usage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Consumption</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes substance consumption (Units)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Use Frequency Interval</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes frequency interval of substance usage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Number of Pack Years</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting the number of pack years</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date and time of Informed Consent</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date and time on which informed consent was signed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Surgical procedure</pageElement>
            <helpText>Medical History Term</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Any Medical History</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating existence of relevant surgical history for the subject</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Start Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the procedure was started</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>HLT Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA High Level Term Name string assigned to the surgical procedure</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>LLT Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA Lowest Level Term Name string assigned to the surgical procedure</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>PT Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA Preferred Term Name string assigned to the surgical procedure</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>SOC Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA System Organ Class Name string assigned to the surgical procedure</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medical history category</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the medical history category</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medical history term</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the medical history term</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Condition Status</pageElement>
            <helpText>A flag indicating condition status (ongoing or not)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medical history start date</pageElement>
            <helpText>A date on which the medical condition was started</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medical history end date</pageElement>
            <helpText>A date on which the medical condition was ended</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medical history PT name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the MedDRA preferred term name string assigned to the medical condition
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medical history HLT name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the MedDRA high level term name string assigned to the medical condition
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medical history SOC name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the MedDRA system organ class name string assigned to the medical
                condition
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medical history LLT name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the MedDRA lowest level term name string assigned to the medical condition
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Surgical procedure start date</pageElement>
            <helpText>A date on which the procedure was started</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Surgical procedure PT name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the MedDRA preferred term name string assigned to the surgical procedure
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Surgical procedure LLT name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the MedDRA lowest level term name string assigned to the surgical
                procedure
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Surgical procedure SOC name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the MedDRA system organ class name string assigned to the surgical
                procedure
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Surgical procedure HLT name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the MedDRA high level term name string assigned to the surgical procedure
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Current medication</pageElement>
            <helpText>A flag indicating that the subject takes medication for the medical condition</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Metastatic/Locally Advanced</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value specifies if cancer locally advanced or metastatic</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Site of Local/Metastatic Disease</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value specifies location of local or metastatic disease</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other Locally Advanced Sites</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value specifies alternative location of local disease</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other Metastatic Sites</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value specifies alternative location of metastatic disease</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Recent Progression Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date of recent progression</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Recurrence of Earlier Cancer (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating that the disease is recurrence of earlier cancer</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver diagnostic investigation</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the method used to perform the liver diagnostic investigation</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver diagnostic investigation date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the liver diagnostic investigation was performed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver diagnostic investigation results</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the results of the liver diagnostic investigation</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Potential Hys law case number</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting potential Hys law case number</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver diagnostic investigation specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the alternative method used to perform the liver diagnostic
                investigation
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Procedure Text</pageElement>
            <helpText>Procedure Text</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MedDRA Preferred Term Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA Preferred Term Name string assigned to the procedure</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MedDRA Lowest Level Term Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA Lowest Level Term Name string assigned to the procedure</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MedDRA High Level Term Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA High Level Term Name string assigned to the procedure</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MedDRA System Organ Class Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA System Organ Class Name string assigned to the procedure</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Procedure Start Date (Time)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date and time on which procedure was started</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Procedure End Date (Time)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date and time on which procedure was ended</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Primary Procedure Reason</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes primary reason for which procedure was performed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Primary Procedure Reason, Other</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes alternative primary reason for which procedure was performed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Procedure Continues at Study Disc/Compl (yes)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating that procedure continues at study disc/compl</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Procedure Reason</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes reason for which procedure was performed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Number of Lesions Resected</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting the number of lesions that was resected</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date Wound Healed</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which wound healed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Hospital Discharge Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the subject was discharged from hospital</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Cause of Death</pageElement>
            <helpText>Disease that caused death</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Designation of cause (primary/secondary)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating that the cause is a primary or secondary</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Autopsy performed (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating that autopsy was performed or was not</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Death related to disease under investigation (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating that death related to disease under investigation or doesn`t</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Cause of Death Narrative</pageElement>
            <helpText>Free text describes cause of death</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Radiotherapy time status (Previous/Current/Post)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Value describes the time of radiotherapy relative to IP</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Chemotherapy time status (Previous/Current/Post)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Value describes the time of chemotherapy relative to IP</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Flag indicating that this is concomitant chemoradiotherapy</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating that this is concomitant chemoradiotherapy</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>The number of prior chemo regimens</pageElement>
            <helpText>he number of prior chemo regimens</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Therapy anti-cancer drug</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes anti-cancer drug used in therapy</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Therapy reason</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes reason why medication was administrated to the subject</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other reason for therapy</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes alternative reason why medication was administrated to the subject</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Route of administration</pageElement>
            <helpText>Route of administration</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Flag indicating that treatment is ongoing</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating that treatment is ongoing</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medication Preferred Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>Medication Preferred Name</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Total Daily Dose</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value giving the dose of medication given to the subject per day</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Dose Unit, Other</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting alternative unit in which the dose is measured</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Multiple Drug (yes)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag to specify that the medication is multiple</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medication Dosing Frequency, Other</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting alternative frequency with which medication is administrated to the subject
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other reason for therapy</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes alternative reason why medication was administrated to the subject</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other Prophylaxis Specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes alternative reason (prophylaxis) why medication was administrated to the
                subject
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason For Treatment Stop</pageElement>
            <helpText>Value describes the reason for Treatment Stop
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason For Treatment Stop, Other</pageElement>
            <helpText>Value describes the other Reason for Treatment Stop
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Infected Body System</pageElement>
            <helpText>Value describes the infected body system
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Infected Body System, Other</pageElement>
            <helpText>Value describes the other infected body system
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Active Ingredient 1</pageElement>
            <helpText>Value describes the active ingredient 1
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Active Ingredient 2</pageElement>
            <helpText>Value describes the active ingredient 2
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Adverse Event Number</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value giving AE number for which medication taken</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Histology type</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes histology type of tumour</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Histology type details</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value giving details about tumour histology type</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Tumour grade</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value specifies tumour grade</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Stage</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value specifies tumour stage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Primary tumour status</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value specifies status of primary tumour</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Nodes status</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value specifies status regional lymph nodes</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Metastases status</pageElement>
            <helpText>Metastases status</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Method of Determination</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes the method of determination</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Other methods</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes an alternative method of determination</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Method</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes used method of ECG</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Treatment Cycle Delayed (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating that treatment cycle was delayed (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason Treatment Cycle Delayed</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes reason why treatment cycle was delayed</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason Treatment Cycle Delayed, Other</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes alternative reason why treatment cycle was delayed</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Laboratory Value Dipstick</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes laboratory value dipstick</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Source type</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes where the data come from. There are two options: Sponsor, Patient</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Device source name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes name of the device through which the data were taken</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Device source version</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes version of the device through which the data were taken</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Device source type</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes type of the device through which the data were taken</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Toxicity Grade</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting toxicity grade</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Subject Visit Number</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number of the subject visit</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of Contact</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date of contact</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Survival Status</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes survival status of the subject</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Date Subject Last Known to be Alive</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the subject was last known alive</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Assessment Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which assessment of performance was made</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Performance Status</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes performance status of the patient</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Questionnaire Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting the questionnaire name that was used for assessment</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Drug</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes trade name/generic name of the drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Route</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes route of administration</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Overdose Start Date (Time)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date and time on which overdose was started</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Overdose Stop Date (Time)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date and time on which overdose was stopped</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Intentional Overdose (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating that overdose was intentional</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Overdose Associated with AE (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag indicating that overdose associated with AE</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Number for AE Associated with Overdose</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting number of AE associated with overdose</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Adverse Event Associated with Overdose</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes CRF text for AE associated with overdose</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Total Dose</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting total dose</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Total Dose Unit</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting unit in which total dose is measured</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Further Information</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes further information (for non SAE)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver risk factor</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the liver risk factor</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver risk factor occurrence (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A flag indicating the liver risk factor occurrence</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver risk factor reference period</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting the liver risk factor reference period (past or current)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver risk factor details</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the details of the liver risk factor</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver risk factor start date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the liver risk factor was started</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver risk factor stop date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the liver risk factor was stopped</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver risk factor comment</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides a liver risk factor comment</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>DLCO (mmol/ kPa x min)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting diffusing capacity of the lung for carbon monoxide</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Total Lung Capacity (TLC (L))</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting total lung capacity (TLC (L))</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>FiO2 (Fraction of Inspired Oxygen)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting fraction of inspired oxygen</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver sign/symptom</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the liver sign/symptom</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver sign/symptom occurrence (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the liver sign/symptom occurrence (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver sign/symptom start date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the liver sign/symptom was started</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver sign/symptom stop date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the liver sign/symptom was stopped</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Intermittent (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A flag indicating that the liver sign/symptom is intermittent (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver sign/symptom specification</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the liver sign/symptom specification</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver sign/symptom text</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting the liver sign/symptom text</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver sign/symptom PT name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA Preferred Term string assigned to the liver sign/symptom</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver sign/symptom LLT name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA Lowest Level Term Name string assigned to the liver sign/symptom</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver sign/symptom HLT name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA High Level Term Name string assigned to the liver sign/symptom</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Liver sign/symptom SOC name</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA System Organ Class string assigned to the liver sign/symptom</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Time Point</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value describes protocol schedule of the measurement</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Heart Rate Value (beats/min)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting heart rate (beats/min)</helpText>
        </help>

        <help>
            <pageElement>Primary cause of death (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Is AE primary cause of death? (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Secondary cause of death (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>Is AE secondary cause of death? (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Additional Drug</pageElement>
            <helpText>Additional Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Caused by Additional Drug (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>AE Caused by Additional Drug (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Additional Drug 1</pageElement>
            <helpText>Additional Drug 1</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Caused by Additional Drug 1 (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>AE Caused by Additional Drug 1 (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Additional Drug 2</pageElement>
            <helpText>Additional Drug 2</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Caused by Additional Drug 2 (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>AE Caused by Additional Drug 2 (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medication Code</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Medication Code of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medication Dictionary text</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Medication Code of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Drug dose ATC Code</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the ATC Code of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Study Drug Total Daily Dose</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value denoting total daily dose of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Study Drug Route</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Route of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>ATC Dictionary Text</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the ATC Dictionary Text of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Study Drug Preferred Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Preferred Name of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Medication Grouping Name</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Pref. Grouping Term of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Active Ingredient</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides an Active Ingredient of Study Drug (more than one can be provided, so
                aggregation should be possible)
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Study Drug Category</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Study Drug Category</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Study Drug ATC Code</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the ATC Code of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Planned Dose</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Planned Dose of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Planned Dose Units</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Planned Dose Units of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Planned No. of Days Treatment</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Planned No. of Days Treatment of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE number caused Action taken</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides an AE number caused Action taken for Study Drug (aggregation should be
                possible)
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Formulation</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Formulation of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Drug dose Route</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Route of Study Drug</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason for Therapy</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the Reason for Therapy</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE number caused Treatment Cycle Delayed</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides an AE number caused Treatment Cycle Delayed (aggregation should be
                possible)
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Protocol schedule timepoint</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the protocol schedule timepoint of the measurement</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of last drug dose</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the drug was taken the last time</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Last drug dose amount</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the last drug dose</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of last dose (Time)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date on which the drug was taken the last time (Time)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Last dose amount</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the last drug dose</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Atrial fibrillation (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A flag indicating if atrial fibrillation is present (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Sinus rhythm (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A flag indicating if sinus rhythm is revealed (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason no sinus rhythm</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the reason of sinus rhythm absence</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Heart rhythm</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the heart rhythm</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Heart rhythm other</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the other heart rhythm</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Extra systoles (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A flag indicating if extra systoles are revealed (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Specify extra systoles</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the specification of extra systoles</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Type of conduction</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the type of conduction</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Conduction</pageElement>
            <helpText>A flag indicating if extra systoles are normal or abnormal</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reason abnormal conduction</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the reason of abnormal conduction</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>ST-T changes (yes/no)</pageElement>
            <helpText>A flag indicating if ST-T changes are revealed (yes/no)</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>ST segment</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the ST segment</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>T-wave</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that describes the T-wave</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Beat group length in sec</pageElement>
            <helpText>The defined duration of a beat group</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Beat group number</pageElement>
            <helpText>The sequential number of the continuous DECG extraction counted across study period</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Beat number within beat group</pageElement>
            <helpText>The sequential number of the individual beat within the continuous DECG extraction</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Number of beats in average beat</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number of beats used to construct the averaged representative wave form</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Beat group length (sec)</pageElement>
            <helpText>The defined duration of a beat group</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Cardiologist comment</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value that provides the cardiologist comment</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MedDRA Lowest Level Term</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA Lowest Level Term Name string assigned to the cause of death</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MedDRA Preferred Term</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA Preferred Term Name string assigned to the cause of death</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MedDRA High Level Term</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA High Level Term Name string assigned to the cause of death</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MedDRA System Organ Class</pageElement>
            <helpText>MedDRA System Organ Class Name string assigned to the cause of death</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE Number</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number assigned to the associated AE record</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event Start Date</pageElement>
            <helpText>The start date of the event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event Start Time</pageElement>
            <helpText>The start time of the event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event Term</pageElement>
            <helpText>The term used to describe the event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event Category 1</pageElement>
            <helpText>The category of cerebrovascular event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event Category 2</pageElement>
            <helpText>The category of cerebrovascular event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event Category 3</pageElement>
            <helpText>The category of cerebrovascular event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event Description 1</pageElement>
            <helpText>Some event Description</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event Description 2</pageElement>
            <helpText>Some event Description</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event Description 3</pageElement>
            <helpText>Some event Description</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Ischemic Symptoms</pageElement>
            <helpText>The category of cardiac ischemic symptoms</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Duration of CIE symptoms</pageElement>
            <helpText>The duration of cardiac ischemic symptoms</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Did the Symptoms Prompt an Uns. Hosp.</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether the symptoms caused an unscheduled hospitalisation</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event Susp. to be Due to Stent Thromb.</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether the symptoms were suspected to be caused by stent thrombosis</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Previous ECG Before Event Available</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether an ECG prior to the event is available</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of Previous ECG</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date of the prior ECG, if any</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>ECG at the Time of the Event</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether an ECG is available at the time of the event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>If no ECG at the Time of Event, Specify</pageElement>
            <helpText>Specify regarding no ECG at the time of the event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Were Local Cardiac Biomarkers Drawn</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether local cardiac biomarkers were drawn</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Coronary Angiography Performed</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether a coronary angiography was performed</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Date of Angiography</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date of coronary angiography</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Final Diagnosis</pageElement>
            <helpText>A category describing the final diagnosis for the CI event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Specify Other Diagnosis</pageElement>
            <helpText>Specification for uncategorised CI event diagnosis</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event description 1</pageElement>
            <helpText>Text describing the event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event description 2</pageElement>
            <helpText>Text describing the event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event description 3</pageElement>
            <helpText>Text describing the event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event description 4</pageElement>
            <helpText>Text describing the event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Event description 5</pageElement>
            <helpText>Text describing the event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Type of Event</pageElement>
            <helpText>The category of cerebrovascular event</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>If Primary Ischemic Stroke</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether it was a primary ischemic stroke</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>If Traumatic</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether the event was traumatic</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Loc. of Primary Intracranial Hemorrhage</pageElement>
            <helpText>Categorical location of the primary intracranial hemorrhage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Primary Intra. Hemorrhage Other, Specify</pageElement>
            <helpText>Specification of uncategorised location of the primary intracranial hemorrhage</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Duration of Symptoms</pageElement>
            <helpText>The duration of the symptoms</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MRS Prior to Stroke</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether subject had MRS prior to stroke</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MRS During Stroke Hospitalisation</pageElement>
            <helpText>Whether subject had MRS during the stroke hospitalisation</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>MRS at Current Visit or 90D After Stroke</pageElement>
            <helpText>MRS at Current Visit or 90D After Stroke</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>AE of Special Interest</pageElement>
            <helpText>Flag to specify that this AE is of particular interest</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Mutation</pageElement>
            <helpText>This field is populated with amino acid change or codon change.
                If no mutations are detected the text for ‘no mutations detected’ should be captured in this field.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <!--69 is Id of the CtDna entity in the MAP_ENTITY table-->
            <!--Tooltip for the Gene field should be displayed only in the CtDna mapping -->
            <pageElement>Gene[69]</pageElement>
            <helpText>This field is not populated (empty) if no mutations are detected.</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Tracked mutation (YES/NO)</pageElement>
            <helpText>‘Tracked mutations‘ can be any subset of mutations (a.a / codon changes) that may or may not be clinically significant.
                This field must be populated with:
                &#9;&#8226; YES - if the mutation is a ‘tracked‘ mutation
                &#9;&#8226; NO - if the mutation is not a ‘tracked‘ mutation</helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>Reported variant allele frequency (VAF)</pageElement>
            <helpText>VAF - must be reported as a ‘fraction‘ value in the data file.
                There will be an option to change the units for the y-axis between ‘fraction‘ and ‘percentage‘.
                The system will perform a calculation if viewing the variant allele frequency as a percentage value on the y-axis.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>report</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colClinicalStudy</pageElement>
            <helpText>The clinical study code that the report data relates to.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDateOfUpload</pageElement>
            <helpText>The date that the study data was uploaded into ACUITY.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colTimeOfUpload</pageElement>
            <helpText>The time that the study data was uploaded into ACUITY.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colDurationOfUpload</pageElement>
            <helpText>The duration of  the ACUITY  data upload process.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colSuccessOfUpload</pageElement>
            <helpText>The Red, Amber or Green status of the upload.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colUploadSummary</pageElement>
            <helpText>A summary description of the data upload
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colAcuityDataSet</pageElement>
            <helpText> the ACUITY  data set collection that the report log message relates to.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colRawDataSource</pageElement>
            <helpText>The original file that the data was in prior to upload into ACUITY.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colSubjectsSource</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number of subjects in the source file.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colSubjectsAcuity</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number of subjects uploaded into ACUITY.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colCurrentTotalValidEvents</pageElement>
            <helpText>The total number of events, e.g. adverse events, lab measurements, dose events etc., in the ACUITY
                system after the upload.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colErrorCount</pageElement>
            <helpText>The number of found errors.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colErrorStatus</pageElement>
            <helpText>The Red, Amber or Green status of the upload.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colAcuityDataField</pageElement>
            <helpText>The ACUITY  data field that the log entry relates to.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colRawDataColumn</pageElement>
            <helpText>The column in the raw file that the log entry relates to.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colErrorType</pageElement>
            <helpText>The type of error, e.g. a mapping error or a data error, that lead to the Red, Amber or Green
                status
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colErrorDetail</pageElement>
            <helpText>A longer description of the Error Type
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colRawDataValue</pageElement>
            <helpText>A value of the field that caused the error.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colEtlStep</pageElement>
            <helpText>The step in the ETL process that threw the exception
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colExceptionType</pageElement>
            <helpText>The Java exception class that threw the exception
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colExceptionMessage</pageElement>
            <helpText>The detailed massage of the exception
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
    <page>
        <pageName>exclusion-values</pageName>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colExclMapping</pageElement>
            <helpText>Pick a data table mapping from which you wish values to be excluded.
                For example, picking ‘Laboratory‘ allows you to exclude certain laboratory test records.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colExclDataField</pageElement>
            <helpText>Pick a data field (equivalent to a table column) from the mapping currently selected
                for which you wish to specify exclusion criteria.
                For example, picking the ‘Laboratory‘ mapping then ‘Subject identifier‘ data field would allow you
                to specify a certain subject ID for whom results will not be shown in the laboratory results.
            </helpText>
        </help>
        <help>
            <pageElement>colExclValue</pageElement>
            <helpText>Pick a value for the the data field that you wish to exclude. For example,
                if you had selected the ‘Laboratory‘ mapping, ‘Subject identifier‘ data field, and value ‘E12345678‘,
                then the subject with that identifier would be excluded from the laboratory test results.
            </helpText>
        </help>
    </page>
</pages>
